zeroto60times.com 2019-09-04

# Privacy Policy, Media Disclaimer & General Site Policies - ZeroTo60Times

## Privacy Policies

Zeroto60times.com is owned and operated by Provectus Media, LLC (“Provectus”) which is committed to providing a web experience that exceeds expectations. This includes maintaining your privacy when it comes to the collection and use of any personally identifiable information you may provide us.  We believe it is important to explain our information gathering practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used.

This privacy policy addresses information that Provectus collects from you, both via the Internet or through other methods, and begins by answering the following questions:

  * What personally identifiable information do we collect, and what are the categories of third-party persons or entities with whom we may share your information?
  * How does Provectus use your information?
  * What is our process for you to review and request changes to your personally identifiable information?
  * How do we notify individuals who use or visit our website of changes to our privacy policies?
  * How do we respond to Web browser “do not track” signals or other mechanisms?

After answering these initial questions, this policy then addresses a number of other issues related to privacy. We suggest that you read this policy in full before providing information to this Provectus website, and that you regularly check our policy to determine if there have been any material changes that would affect your decision on whether to continue using this website.

**What information does Provectus collect?**

When you send comments, questions, suggestions or feedback to Provectus via email, and include an email address or any other contact information, Provectus will use this information to respond to you. This website will not ever sell or disclose your contact information to any third parties. We collect basic analytical data about our visitors for the sole purpose of optimizing our site to better serve our much appreciated guests.  Provectus does not collect user statistics of which would disclose the identities of the site’s visitors.

We may collect certain information automatically as you use our websites, such as your Internet Protocol address, browser type, computer type, operating system version, type of mobile device (if used), location data (if available), the time and date associated with your use of our website, the pages on our website that you view and how long you view each page, as well as other miscellaneous information about you.

To enhance your online experience, we use “cookies.” Cookies are text files we place in your computer’s browser to store your preferences. Once you choose to furnish the site with personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie, and to personalize your experience on our website.

We use cookies to understand Internet usage and to improve our content, offerings, and advertisements. Provectus will use cookies, pixel trackers, server logs and other Internet technologies to measure the effectiveness of our website content.

We may have enabled Demographic & Interest reporting via Google Analytics Advertising Features for some of our websites. This information is used to better understand how our website visitors are interacting with the site. This information is not used to personally identify any website visitors. Visitors can opt-out of Google Analytics Advertiser Features through Ads Settings, Ad Settings for mobile apps, or any other available means (for example, the NAI’s consumer opt-out). Google also provides a listing of currently available opt-outs for the web.

We also may use small pieces of code called “web beacons” or “clear gifs” to collect anonymous and aggregate advertising metrics, such as counting page views. We are not responsible for and do not control cookies placed in third party ads or any actions or policies of any third party advertising technology service providers or of any third party members of any related advertising networks.

**How does Provectus share information?**

Provectus reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on Provectus. We may also share information when we have a good faith belief it is necessary to prevent fraud or other illegal activity, to prevent imminent bodily harm, or to prevent harm to Provectus, or our users. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, courts, or other government entities.

Additionally, if the ownership of all or substantially all of our business changes or we otherwise transfer assets relating to our business or the websites to a third party, we may transfer your personal information to the new owner to be used consistent with this policy.

Provectus may also engage certain trusted third party companies and individuals to facilitate the website on Provectus’s behalf, to perform services (e.g., without limitation, hosting and maintenance services, web analytics, and database storage and management services). We may share your personally identifiable information with these third parties to the extent necessary to perform these functions and provide such services.

**How does Provectus use my information?**

Information volunteered by you in any message or postings (e.g. Disqus), or the like, becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information in any such posted message.  Information volunteered by you in any email message to Provectus will be used to respond and address your inquiry.

**How does Provectus notify visitors of privacy policy changes?**

If Provectus decides to make any changes to our privacy policy, we will notify you by posting the new privacy policy on the website. You are responsible for consulting this policy regularly to determine Provectus’s current privacy policy, as well as to determine if there are any changes to the prior version(s) of Provectus’s privacy policy.

**Our Policy for Children Under 13**

This website is not directed to children under the age of 13. Provectus does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children. If a parent or guardian becomes aware that his or her child has provided us with personally identifiable information without parental consent, he or she should contact us. If we become aware that a child under the age of 13 has provided us with personally identifiable information without verifiable parental consent, we will delete such information from our files.

## Media Disclaimer

IMPORTANT: Zeroto60Times.com is not affiliated, sponsored or in any way associated with the automotive manufactures listed on this site. The “Nominative Fair Use” of trademarks contained in this site are merely intended to aid users in the discovery and proper identification of brands and eliminate any potential confusion amongst brands. All logos and trademarks within Zeroto60Times.com are the sole property of their respective trademark owners and are in no way authorized by, sponsored by, or associated with this website. Zeroto60Times does not recommend any brand over another.

## General Website Policies

Zeroto60Times.com offers a comprehensive directory of 0-60 and quarter mile automotive statistics, gathered from both domestic and international sources.  Although the information in this site has been carefully assembled with accuracy as a top priority, neither the precision nor the validly of any information in this site is guaranteed in any way.

Neither Zeroto60Times.com’s publisher, agents, servants nor any affiliate thereof assumes any responsibility or liability for any loss, injury or damage (including, but not limited to, consequential, actual, punitive or incidental damages).  The information in this site is in no way intended to be trusted, nor relied upon for any reason. Hence, Zeroto60Times.com shall on no account accept liability for the consequences of the use of information within or derived from this website.  Information on Zeroto60Times.com is provided merely for entertainment value, and should never be relied upon as a resource to base decisions upon.

Zeroto60Times.com reserves the right to transform, delete and add information at any time and for any reason. This website does not guarantee to function at all times. Zeroto60Times.com is by no means sponsored, nor affiliated with any automotive manufacturer, dealer, parts retailer or other automotive company of any kind. This website does not represent, warrant, nor endorse the accuracy or reliability of the information, content or advertisements in the site.

Zeroto60Times.com and its content is copyright of Provectus Media, LLC. All rights reserved. Any redistribution or reproduction of part or all of the contents in any form is prohibited other than the following: (1) You may print or download to a local hard disk extracts for your personal and non-commercial use only (2) You may copy the content to individual third parties for their personal use, but only if you acknowledge the website as the source of the material. You may not, except with our express written permission, distribute or commercially exploit the content on Zeroto60Times.com. Nor may you transmit it or store it in any other website or other form of electronic retrieval system. We will pursue copyright violations to the fullest extent of the law.

In reading these policies, you hereby acknowledge that any reliance upon any information contained in Zeroto60Times.com shall be limited to your own risk.
